Bills on the counter
Plate in the sink
Phone on low battery
No time to think
Empty in the closet
Shoes got tape
I keep looking at the week
Like it might escape
Tell me what you need
I know what I need
A little more room
A little more speed
More money, more money
(I need it now)
(I need it somehow)
More money, more money
Keep the wolves outside
Let me breathe tonight
Mama on the line
Saying hold your head
I’m counting every dollar
Before I go to bed
Gas light blinking
Rent due soon
I make a little magic
Out of bad news
Tell me what you need
I know what I need
A little more room
A little more speed
More money, more money
(I need it now)
(I need it somehow)
More money, more money
Keep the wolves outside
Let me breathe tonight
I’m tired of the stretch
Tired of the wait
Tired of making dreams
Fit in a takeout plate
One more break
One more win
Let the whole world change
When the pay comes in
More money, more money
(I need it now)
(I need it somehow)
More money, more money
Keep the wolves outside
Let me breathe tonight